(Bernadette:)Hey, I learned a long time ago,
when you're four feet eleven
(Bernadette:)and eye level
with every guy's crotch,
(Bernadette:)that's where you punch.
(Penny:)That's funny.
(Penny:)I learned something
totally different.
(Bernadette:)Do you know what?
(Bernadette:)It's just a research project.
(Bernadette:)The most important job
in the world
(Bernadette:)is gonna be raising this child.
(Bernadette:)It's all I need
to give my life meaning.
(Penny:)Oh, that's so beautiful.
(Bernadette:)You believe me? Oh, good.
(Bernadette:)11 more chumps like you,
(Bernadette:)I'll have the jury
eating out of my hand.
(Sheldon:)I never realized
this building was classified.
(Howard:)Maybe that's because
it's classified.
(Leonard:)Wish we weren't so far
from my parking space.
(Sheldon:)The way you put away
those lemon bars,
(Sheldon:)perhaps that's a good thing.
(Leonard:)I'd like to reinstate
the you-not-talking rule.
(Sheldon:)Why? It clearly doesn't work.
(Howard:)I guess this is it.
(Leonard:)Is that a retinal scanner?
(Howard:)Let's find out.